<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<root>
    <field>
        <name>Carmen Mañón</name>
        <en>Carmen Mañón, born in Mexico, is a talented singer of Latin American music who currently resides in New York City. With a captivating voice and a unique style, Carmen has stood out for her ability to convey the feelings and emotions of Latin songs. Passionate about her art, Carmen finds deep satisfaction in sharing the nostalgia and joy that characterize Latin music, thus reaching the hearts of her audience. Through her music, Carmen Mañón brings harmony and happiness to those who have the privilege of listening to her, leaving a lasting mark on the world of Latin American music.</en>
        <es>Carmen Mañón, nacida en México, es una talentosa cantante de música latinoamericana que actualmente reside en la ciudad de Nueva York. Con una voz cautivadora y un estilo único, Carmen se ha destacado por su habilidad para transmitir los sentimientos y emociones de las canciones latinas. Apasionada por su arte, Carmen encuentra una profunda satisfacción en compartir la nostalgia y la alegría que caracterizan a la música latina, llegando así a los corazones de su audiencia. A través de su música, Carmen Mañón trae armonía y felicidad a quienes tienen el privilegio de escucharla, dejando una huella perdurable en el mundo de la música latinoamericana.</es>
    </field>
    <field>
        <name>Marco Spíndola</name>
        <en>Marco Spíndola is a versatile Mexican artist, photographer, scene director, and guitarist. With over 30 years of experience as an educator, Marco has been a source of inspiration for individuals of all ages - from children to the elderly - in the fields of music, theater, and performing arts. Marco's extensive career in education includes teaching at various schools in Mexico, Costa Rica, Canada, and the United States.</en>
        <es>Marco Spíndola es un versátil artista mexicano, fotógrafo, director de escena y guitarrista. Con más de 30 años de experiencia como educador, Marco ha sido fuente de inspiración en personas de todas las edades, desde niños hasta ancianos, en los ámbitos de la música, el teatro y las artes escénicas. La amplia trayectoria de Marco en su trabajo pedagógico incluye la enseñanza en diversas escuelas de México, Costa Rica, Canadá y Estados Unidos.</es>
    </field>
    <field>
        <name>Nicolas Carter</name>
        <en>Nicolas Carter is a Paraguayan harpist, educator, storyteller, and bilingual and bicultural theatre artist. Nicolas has composed, recorded, and performed harp music internationally for 35 years and has recorded over a dozen albums as a solo artist and with Latin American and world music ensembles. He is often featured as a concert performer and master teacher at national and international harp festivals.</en>
        <es>Nicolas Carter es un arpista Paraguayo, educador, narrador y artista teatral bilingüe y bicultural. Nicolás ha compuesto, grabado e interpretado música de arpa a nivel internacional durante 35 años y ha grabado más de una docena de álbumes como solista y con conjuntos de música latinoamericana. A menudo aparece como concertista y maestro en festivales de arpa nacionales e internacionales.</es>
    </field>
</root>